Finding Aid for Nellie May Davis Finley Family Papers
Clarke Historical Library
- Nellie May Davis Finley Family Papers.
  - Correspondence to: NDF, W. H. Davis From: Harry C. Finley,May 2, 8, 23, 30, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 248)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Flossie Foster,May 12, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 249)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Gerty Davis,May 9, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 250)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Grace Carleton,May 15, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 251)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Meda Burgess,May 15, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 252)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Auntie Lida Miller,May 17, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 253)
  - Correspondence to: W. H. Davis, NDF From: Harry and Zoe Davis,May 18, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 254)
  - Correspondence to: Harry and Zoe Davis From: Theron W. Finley,May 20, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 255)
  - Correspondence to: NDF, W. H. Davis From: Theron W. Finley,May 20, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 256)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Jennie Slack Cook,May 27, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 257)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,June 5, 12, 20, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 258)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,June 27, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 259)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Auntie Lida Miller,June 1, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 260)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry and Zoe Davis,June 2, 14, 23, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 261)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Theron W. Finley,June 20, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 262)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,July 5, 10, 19, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 263)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,July 27, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 264)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry and Zoe Davis,July 6, 23, 26, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 265)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Fred McMurtrie,July 7, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 266)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Mary J. Peckham,July 13, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 267)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Mrs. Lynn Olson,July 11, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 268)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Gerty Davis,July 12, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 269)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Sara,August 1, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 270)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Gerty Davis,August 9, 16, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 271)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry and Zoe Davis,August 11, 17, 25, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 272)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry and Zoe Davis,August 31, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 273)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Mina Wilder Atkins,August 2, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 274)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Aunt Louie Thompson,August 5, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 275)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Amy Ruff,August 7, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 276)
  - Correspondence to: Harry C. Finley From: Michigan College of Mining and Technology,August 8, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 277)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Gertrude Harrington,August 16, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 278)
  - Correspondence to: Harry C. Finley From: Harold D. Cullum,August 18, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 279)
  - Correspondence to: Harry C. Finley From: Carson,August 19, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 280)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Theron W. Finley,August 28, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 281)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry and Zoe Davis,September 8, 22, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 282)
  - Correspondence to: Harry C. Finley From: Bob Steveling,September 16, 27, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 283)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Jessie,September 1, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 284)
  - Correspondence to: Harry C. Finley From: Alice, includes photograph,September 5, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 285)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Maud E. Grill, Jackson County Library,September 6, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 286)
  - Correspondence to: Harry C. Finley From: War Department, Regular Army Reserves,August 8, 14, 17, 25, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 287)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Charles S. Crittenden,September 9, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 288)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Frederick McMurtrie,September 14, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 289)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Meda Burgess,September 15, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 290)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Order of the Eastern Star,September 21, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 291)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Aunt Louie Thompson,September 27, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 292)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Dorothy,September 28, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 293)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Auntie Lida Miller,October 2, 17, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 294)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Zarita,October 13, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 295)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,October 7, 16, 21, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 296)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,October 30, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 297)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry and Zoe Davis,October 11, 20, 25, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 298)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry and Zoe Davis,October [no day], 1938 (Box 14, Folder 299)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Mary Belle,October 24, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 300)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Gerty and Wilson Davis,October 30, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 301)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Aunt Louie Thompson,November 1, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 302)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Dorothy Snider,November 2, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 303)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Theron W. Finley,November 6, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 304)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,November 6, 13, 29, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 305)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Huberts Greenhouse,November 7, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 306)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Gerty Davis,November 9, 12, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 307)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry and Zoe Davis,November 10, 28, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 308)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Fred and Rose McMurtrie,November 14, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 309)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Zoe Thatcher,November 22, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 310)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Meda Burgess,November 26, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 311)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Jennie Slack Cook,November 27, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 312)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry E. Davis,November 30, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 313)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry and Zoe Davis,December 7, 12, 28, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 314)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Auntie Lida Miller,December 9, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 315)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: "Ma" Honeywell,December 10, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 316)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. Louie Thompson From: Harry C. Finley,December 11, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 317)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Zoe Thatcher,December 14, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 318)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Amy Ruff,December 15, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 319)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Lorraine, Peter, and Gayle Geuye?,December 15, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 320)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Zoe Davis,December 15, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 321)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry E. Davis,December 16, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 322)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Mary Belle and Billy,December 17, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 323)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Theron W. Finley,December 27, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 324)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Flossie Foster,December 28, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 325)
  - Correspondence to: Harry C. Finley From: Earl Fox,December 29, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 326)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Meda Burgess,January 2, 27, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry and Zoe Davis,January 5, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,January 4, 15, 22, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Gerty Davis,January 15, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Alice Gault,January 17, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence to: W. H. Davis From: Theron W. Finley,January 22, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence to: Aunt Louie Thompson From: Harry C. Finley,January 29, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Auntie Miller,January 29, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry and Zoe Davis,February 2, 8, 23, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,February 6, 14, 19, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,February 27, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Gerty Davis,February 1, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Thelma,February 6, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Fred and Rose McMurtrie,February 19, 28, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: L. Olmsted,February 27, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Gertie (Palmer?),February 27, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Geraldine and Harold Gumbert,February 28, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Theron W. Finley,March 5-6, 12, 22, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Theron W. Finley,March 26, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,March 5, 12, 28, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Mary J. and Bernice Peckham,March 2, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence to: NDF, Aunt Louie Thompson From: Zoe Davis,March 14, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence to: Uncle Harry and Aunt Zoe Davis From: Theron W. Finley,March 5, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Meda Burgess,March 5, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Gerty, Marydena, and Wilson Davis,February 28, March 5, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Matie and Jud, Mrs. Perry,March 6, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry and Zoe Davis,March 2, 7-8, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Sarah Greenman,March 8, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 2289)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Narcorosie,March 8, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Narcorosie,March 8, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Bertha Thompson,March 13, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: H. S. Don Carlos,March 13, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Auntie Miller,March 19, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Grace Waterman,March 20, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Louisa Wheeler,March 21, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Flossie Foster,March 24, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Alice Gault,March 27, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Ethel,March 31, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry and Zoe Davis,March 17 and April 11, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry and Zoe Davis,April 21, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Gerty Davis,April 7, 20, 25, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,April 2,9, 16, 25, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,April 30, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Maude Crittenden,April 3, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Amy Ruff,April 2, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 45)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Meda Burgess,April 15, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 46)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Zoe Davis,April 17, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 47)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Sarah Greenman,April 18, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 48)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Sarah Greenman,April 19, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 49)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Aunt Louie Thompson,May 3, 19, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 50)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Zarita Saxton,May 10, 16, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 51)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Bertie McMurtrie,May 15, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 52)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry and Zoe Davis,May 7, 13, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 53)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Gerty Davis,May 7, 9, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 54)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Zoe Davis, Ruth Saxton,May 2, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 55)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Zoe Thatcher,May 6, 14, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 56)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Ethel and Laverne,May 16, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 57)
  - Correspondence to: Gerty Davis From: Aunt Nellie Finley (NDF),May 13, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 58)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Amy Ruff,May 19, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 59)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,May 14, 19, 21, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 60)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,May 28, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 61)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Dorothy Hicks,May 31, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 62)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Amy Ruff,June 9, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 63)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Aunt Louie Thompson,June 9, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 64)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,June 4, 11, 20, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 65)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,June 25, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 66)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Bertie McMurtrie,June 12, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 67)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Zarita Saxton,June 13, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 68)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Meda Burgess,June 21, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 69)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Theron W. Finley,June 25, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 70)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Gerty Davis,June 27, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 71)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Gerty Davis,June 28, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 72)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry and Zoe Davis,June 29, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 73)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry and Zoe Davis,June 6, 12, 21, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 74)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry and Zoe Davis,July 25, 28, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 75)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,July 2, 14, 18, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 76)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Sylvia Chappell,July 2, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 77)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Gerty Davis, includes Photograph,July 2, 22, 25, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 78)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Aunt Louie Thompson,June 9, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 79)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: M. and L. Gribbles,July 19, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 80)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Lida Miller,July 21, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 81)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,August 6, 16, 20, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 82)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry and Zoe Davis,August 3, 8, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 83)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry and Zoe Davis,September 2, 26, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 84)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Lida J. Miller,September 3, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 85)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Meda Burgess,September 3, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 86)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Zoe Davis,September 7, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 87)
  - Correspondence to: NDF, Harry C. Finley From: Gerty Davis and All,September 10, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 88)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry Zoe and Davis,October 10, 13, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 89)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Theron W. Finley,October 19, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 90)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Theron W. Finley,November 10, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 91)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Aunt Louie Thompson,October 4, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 92)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Aunt Louie Thompson,October 10, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 93)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Zoe Thatcher,October 15, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 94)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Marvin O. Hall,October 27, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 95)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,October 3, 8, 15, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 96)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,October 22, 29, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 97)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,November 5, 12, 19, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 98)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,November 24, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 99)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,December 1, 9, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 100)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: "Ma" Honeywell,December 1, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 101)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Dorothy Hicks,[no month, day] 194u (Box 15, Folder 102)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,January 13, 20, 28, 1940 (Box 15, Folder 103)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: "Ma" Honeywell,January 18, 1940 (Box 15, Folder 104)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,February 3, 10, 17, 1940 (Box 15, Folder 105)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,February 25-26, 1940 (Box 15, Folder 106)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Rose Blodgett,February 7, 1940 (Box 15, Folder 107)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Zoe and Harry Davis,February 17, 194u (Box 15, Folder 108)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,March 3, 9, 17, 30, 1940 (Box 15, Folder 109)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: "Ma" Honeywell,March 6, 1940 (Box 15, Folder 110)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Dorothy Hicks,March 18, 1940 (Box 15, Folder 111)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,April 6, 13, 20, 1940 (Box 15, Folder 112)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,April 22-23, 27, 1940 (Box 15, Folder 113)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,May 3, 12, 16, 1940 (Box 15, Folder 114)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,May 21, 25, 30, 1940 (Box 15, Folder 115)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,June 11, 27, 1940 (Box 15, Folder 116)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,July 1, 12, 1940 (Box 15, Folder 117)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry and Zoe Davis,July 30, 1940 (Box 15, Folder 118)
  - Correspondence to: Harry C. Finley From: Ted Walker,August 26, 1940 (Box 15, Folder 119)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,September 11, 30, 1940 (Box 15, Folder 120)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Theron W. Finley,September 6, 1940 (Box 15, Folder 121)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,October 6, 11, 21, 1940 (Box 15, Folder 122)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,October 25, 1940 (Box 15, Folder 123)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,November 3, 10, 17, 1940 (Box 15, Folder 124)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,November 27, 1940 (Box 15, Folder 125)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Theron W. Finley,November 9, 1940 (Box 15, Folder 126)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,December 2, 7, 15, 1940 (Box 15, Folder 127)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Mr. and Mrs. Ard A. Ludlow,[no month, day], 1941 (Box 15, Folder 128)
  - Correspondence to: Harry C. Finley From: Dorothy Hicks,[no month, day], 1941 (Box 15, Folder 129)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,January 12, 26, 1941 (Box 15, Folder 130)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley, includes Photographs, 1944,February 2,9, 16, 1941, 1944 (Box 15, Folder 131)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,March 2, 10, 18, 1941 (Box 15, Folder 132)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,March 24, 30, 1941 (Box 15, Folder 133)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Theron W. Finley,March 30, 1941 (Box 15, Folder 134)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,April 7, 13, 20, 1941 (Box 15, Folder 135)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,April 24, 1941 (Box 15, Folder 136)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,May 5, 13, 20, 1941 (Box 15, Folder 137)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,May 25, 1941 (Box 15, Folder 138)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Aunt Louie Thompson,May 27, 1941 (Box 15, Folder 139)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Bud Klenner, and reply from NDF,May 5, 1941 (Box 15, Folder 140)
  - Correspondence to: Harry C. Finley From: Merle,June 6, 1941 (Box 15, Folder 141)
  - Correspondence to: Harry C. Finley From: Ruth Saxton,June 4, 1941 (Box 15, Folder 142)
  - Correspondence to: Harry C. Finley From: George and Kay,June 5, 1941 (Box 15, Folder 143)
  - Correspondence to: unidentified From: Harry C. Finley,June 6, 1941 (Box 15, Folder 144)
  - Correspondence to: Harry C. Finley From: Mother (NDF),June 19, 1941 (Box 15, Folder 145)
  - Correspondence to: Harry C. Finley From: A. N. MacIntosh,June 20, 1941 (Box 15, Folder 146)
  - Correspondence to: Harry C. Finley From: Aunt Louie Thompson,June 21, 1941 (Box 15, Folder 147)
  - Correspondence to: Harry C. Finley From: Bill,June 21, 1941 (Box 15, Folder 148)
  - Correspondence to: Harry C. Finley From: Mom (NDF),June 24, 1941 (Box 15, Folder 149)
  - Correspondence to: Harry C. Finley From: Harry and Zoe Davis,June 25, 1941 (Box 15, Folder 150)
  - Correspondence to: Harry C. Finley From: Don Harrington,July 6, 1941 (Box 15, Folder 151)
  - Correspondence to: Harry C. Finley From: Edward R. Kubilins,July 17, 1941 (Box 15, Folder 152)
  - Correspondence to: Harry C. Finley From: Mom (NDF),July 26, 1941 (Box 15, Folder 153)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,August 4, 6, 11, 19, 1941 (Box 15, Folder 154)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,August 24, 1941 (Box 15, Folder 155)
  - Correspondence to: Harry C. Finley From: Mother (NDF),August 3, 1941 (Box 15, Folder 156)
  - Correspondence to: Harry C. Finley From: Mother (NDF), includes Photographs,August 18, 1941 (Box 15, Folder 157)
  - Correspondence to: Harry C. Finley From: Aunt Louie Thompson,August 20, 1941 (Box 15, Folder 158)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Dorothy Hicks,September 22, 27, 30, 1941 (Box 15, Folder 159)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,September 1, 17, 25, 1941 (Box 15, Folder 160)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,September 29, 1941 (Box 15, Folder 161)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,October 2, 9, 11, 1941 (Box 15, Folder 162)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,October 12, 25, 1941 (Box 15, Folder 163)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,November 1, 10, 20, 1941 (Box 15, Folder 164)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,November 30, 1941 (Box 15, Folder 165)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Theron W. Finley,November 7, 1941 (Box 15, Folder 166)
  - Correspondence to: Mr. and Mrs. Frederick J. McMurtrie From: Harry C. Finley,November 13, 1941 (Box 15, Folder 167)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,December 11, 21, 1941 (Box 15, Folder 168)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Edna,December 30, 1941 (Box 15, Folder 169)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,January 4, 10, 21, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 170)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,January 29, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 171)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Theron W. Finley,January 18, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 172)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,February 7, 12, 18, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 173)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,February 24, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 174)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. Frederick J. McMurtrie From: Harry C. Finley,February 5, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 175)
  - Correspondence to: Gerty, Wilson, and Marydena Davis From: Harry C. Finley,February 13, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 176)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Dorothy Hicks,March 9, 19, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 177)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,March 2, 7, 15, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 178)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,March 23, 28, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 179)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Theron W. Finley,March 9, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 180)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,April 2, 8, 16, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 181)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,April 20, 29, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 182)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Jerry,April 24, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 183)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,May 3, 7, 11, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 184)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,May 17, 23, 30, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 185)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,June 6, 10, 17, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 186)